https://mindvision-records.com/privacy-policy/

close Close
HomeReleasesArtistsBlogShopCartCheckoutMy AccountContact
HomeReleasesArtistsBlogShopCartCheckoutMy AccountContact Home/Privacy Policy
menu
chevron_right
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyMindVision-Records.com is compliant with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679.It means that we are open about our methods of tracking and use of the visitors’ personal data, and you can freely check what exactly we’re doing to it.At MindVision-Records.com, we collect:Your name and surnameYour email addressYour physical addressYour phone numberThe data about the browser and device you use to view the storeThe way you navigate the storeWe gather your contact details because they are necessary to accept and process your orders, and to make sure you’ve got your packages.We gather the details of your technical equipment and on-site behavior in order to make our store more user-friendly, and to personalize our store services for you (for example, to automatically switch the store to the mobile version.)Our store works with outer companies that help us provide the best service for you, and these third parties also use some of the personal details you’re leaving. We limit the data they can access to only what is necessary for them to perform their obligations.Payment services use your credit card number, your name and surname to verify and process your payments for our productsOur manufacturers and stock keepers use the data of your order contents to assemble the necessary package for youPostal services use your first name, last name, and physical address to arrange the product delivery for youMass mailing services use your email address to send you emails (if you have subscribed for them)If you keep browsing our webstore after reading this Privacy Policy, you give us the consent to use your personal details for the purposes explained above.If you don’t agree to these terms, please leave the website.You can email us at contact@mindvision-records.com and ask:To receive the copy of your personal details we have collectedTo delete your personal details from our systemTo withdraw your consent (if you previously agreed to provide us with the data, but then changed your mind)We are doing our best to guarantee the security of your personal details while keeping and using them.Thank you for your cooperation!Recent Posts ADRIATIC Lounge Vol 2 – Croatian Finest Chill Out / Lounge Music Adriatic Lounge vol.1 Adriatic House Session vol.1 ARCfusion – Life is touching Preview Video 2funk – Something around me Preview VIDEOARTISTS
2funk
[Croatia]
ARCfusion
[Croatia]
© All Rights Reserved. MindVision Records 2020.HomeAbout usTerms and conditionsPrivacy PolicyContactShopCartCheckoutMy Account Go to album
